# **Andreas Marsh**

Computer Science Honors Undergraduate Student

### **SUMMARY**

I am a third-year honors student at the University of Georgia studying Computer Science and have training and experience in both Java, C++, and Swift programming.

I am a bright critical thinker with a proven talent for learning quickly in results-oriented environments.

Through years of working at summer camps, I have developed great leadership, communication, and teamwork skills, being able to create environments where everybody feels both included and valued.

### **EXPERIENCE**



# **Glisson Camp & Retreat Center**, Dahlonega, GA — *Camp Counselor*

May 2019 - July 2019

- worked with children and adults with mild to moderate developmental disabilities
- created an environment that uplifted campers and allowed their uniqueness to shine



# **Glisson Camp & Retreat Center,** Dahlonega, GA — *Camp Crew*

May 2018 - July 2018

- performed various jobs and tasks around camp to have it run smoothly
- lifeguarded, helped facilitate high ropes course, set up and cleaned the dining hall, and other jobs
- had a major impact on preparing me for college and how to balance a schedule, work within a group, and gain an overall greater understanding of managing the new independence and responsibilities you're given in college

## **EDUCATION**



# **The University of Georgia,** Athens, GA — BS Computer Science

August 2018 - May 2022

### **CONTACT**

124 North Poplar St Athens, GA, 30601 (404) 502-0710 marsh.andreas.s@gmail.com

### **WEBSITE**

andreasmarsh.com

### **SKILLS**

Java

C++

**Swift** 

**Application Design** 

**Software Design** 

**Problem Solving** 

### **HONORS & AWARDS**

Honors Program Member of UGA's Honor Program August 2018 - Present

Dean's List

Spring Semester 2020

Charter Scholarship Recipient Awarded for outstanding achievement in academics to 2% of new students

### **LANGUAGES**

English (high proficiency)German (moderate proficiency)